买一
Numero uno.
- 好了 - 让他2分钟后过来
- You're on. - Send him over to me in two minutes.
常输的人也会有赢的时候
Although the joker could turn out to be the ace in the pack.
赢了 厉害
Get in there,my son!
不能把他们全赢光啊 Joe
Can't win them all,Joe.
有问题?
Problem?
那人是我丈夫
That's my husband.
谢谢各位
Thank you,chaps.
本作品由Norm HALFCD Team倾情奉献\N感谢原作提供资源.仅供学习交流.严禁用于商业行为\N请自觉于下载后24小时内删除!如果喜欢本片,请购买正版!
更多精彩 尽在www.NormTeam.com
压制:鬼谷子  字幕:鬼谷子\NCompression:GV-Sir  Subtitles:GV-Sir
飞天大盗 第2季第5集
S02E05 Old Acquaintance
怎样?
So?
赌场的计划先放一边
The casino score's on hold.
我们找到了新目标
We've got ourselves a new mark.
- 谁? - Jake Henry
- Who? - Jake Henry.
我丈夫
My husband.
五年前他
He walked out on me five years ago...
把我所有的一切都带走了
with pretty much everything I owned.
所有?
Everything?
把我重要的东西都带走了 只给我留下一些感触的东西
Apart from a few thoughtful touches,he took all the things that mattered to me.
- 连我的屋都拿走了 - 人渣
- Even my home. - Bastard.
他给我留下一张Phil Collins的CD 那倒不是我的
He left me a Phil Collins CD that wasn't even mine.
- 变态的人渣 - 我要说的是 这是个报复的机会
- Twisted bastard. - The point is,it's payback time.
那我们有什么消息?
So what do we know?
- Ash? - 我现在还不是很清楚
- Ash? - Well,I haven't had that much time.
我只知道他刚从Amsterdam过来 这边住几个星期
But I have found out he's only in town from Amsterdam for a few days...
来玩玩牌,德州扑克
to play poker.Texas hold 'em.
他今晚在赌场还有另外一场赌局
And he's got another game at the casino tonight.
他是在玩玩还是在骗人?
He playing for real or pulling a con?
- Jake这样的人很可能是在骗人 - 的确 应该是这样
- Probably the latter,knowing Jake. - Well,it looked like it was for real.
据说他是最好的几个老千
And word is he's one of the best.
现在还是吗?
Is he,now?
- 他在哪住? - Aylesham酒店
- Where's he staying? - The Aylesham.
那他要不是很有钱 要么就是他 根本没打算给钱罗
So either he's worth a few quid or he's planning not to pay.
那我们怎么办?
What's our in?
我们得快一点动手 所以还是用赌牌吧
We'll have to move fast,so it'll have to be the poker.
根据之前的表现 Danny能继续当我们的无助酒鬼
Going on previous performances,Danny can play our hopeless drunk...
- 没多大问题 - 是吗?谢谢
- without too much difficulty. - Yeah?Thank you.
你得知道 要做好那酒鬼
I'll have you know it does take a lot of hard work and dedication...
还得花很多功夫跟努力喔
to be that convincing.
我们说服Jake来赌一场德州扑克
So we'll convince Jake to join us in a holdem competition.
- 我们还要知道什么? - 如果有人拥有Jake想要的东西
- Anything else we should know? - lf someone's got something Jake wants...
他就会不惜一切的把它骗到手
he'll do whatever he can to take it off them.
我们就迎合他这性格好了
So we'll rekindle his desire for something.
这样的话 Stacie你是鱼饵
In this case,Stacie.
你别这么轻易跟他走了喔
You watch he don't get carried away.
好了 跟昨晚一样
Okay,same routine as last night.
Albert 你去牵引一下 Stacie跟我等你的消息
Albert,you'll rope.Stacie and I will wait for the signal.
Danny你还做那酒鬼 Ash 周围走走 看还有什么信息
Danny,as you were.Ash,dig around,see what else you can find out.
好 好了 你们都有些好玩的事干
Yeah,that's right.You lot do the glamorous stuff...
我就做这无足轻重的事 干嘛你不去?
and leave me to do the serious graft,why don't you?
我们开始吧
Let's get started.
Stace 我能跟你谈谈吧?
Stace,can I have a word?
- 能啊 - 听着
- Yeah. - Look...
我知道你可能也不想这样
I understand if you don't want to do this...
但只有你最了解他
but you know him better than anybody else.
我还得了解一下他
I just need a bit more going.
29 好啊29 赢你14
Twenty-nine!Big 29!Big 14!
赢你9点
Big nine!Come on,baby!
我见你之前也赢过 你蛮厉害的喔
I saw you winning earlier.You're quite a player.
谢谢
Thanks.
我叫Ben Morgan 有时玩玩牌 有时小赌一下
Ben Morgan.Sometime poker player,sometime blackjack player...
- 有时也会赢 - Jake Henry 总是赢的
- sometime a winner. - Jake Henry.All the time winner.
这我相信
That I can believe,yes.
Benny小帅哥 好吗?
Benny the Ball,all right,son?
继续 为了我们的小酒鬼 干杯 宝贝
Hang on,just get our little drinky-poos.Cheers,babe.
- 我不记得你的名字 - 因为我没给过你
- I didn't catch your name,mate. - I didn't give it out.
我以前没见过你吧?
I've not seen you round here before,have I?
应该没有 我昨天刚到
Unlikely.I only arrived here yesterday.
这是Jake Henry 他是个赌牌好手 他很忙的
This is Jake Henry.And he's an excellent poker player and a very busy man.
- 今晚玩的好吧 Jake? - 蛮好
- Having a good night,are you,Jake? - I was.
就像我说的 Henry先生是个大忙人
Like I said,Mr.Henry is a very busy man.
好的 迟些见 Jack
All right,whatever.Anyway,catch you later,Jack.
迟些见 Benny 明晚 别忘了
I'll see you later,Benny.Tomorrow night,don't forget.
我就知道你爱忘事
I know what you're like,Mr.Forgetful.
麻烦人 千万别告诉他什么
Nightmare.Don't tell him anything.
好的 我的心肝
All right,sweetheart?
怎么想也不会把你们两联系到一起
I wouldn't have thought you and he moved in the same circles.
我们没关系的 我只是认识他父亲
Oh,we don't.I know his father...
或者说跟他爸在高尔夫球场上见过几次面
or rather,made his acquaintance at a golf charity function.
他很无聊的 可就是有钱 所以认识一下也无防
He's a terrible bore,but a billionaire,and therefore useful to know.
他儿子就老是以为自己是赌牌高手
His son thinks he's one of the hotshots on the poker circuit.
老喜欢跟最好的高手玩
He's always trying to mingle with the best players.
如果赌牌的以为自己能赢所有高手
If the joker's dumb enough to think he can beat the best players...
那他就活该输的精光
he deserves to lose every penny he's got.
常输的也会有时赢的
Although the joker could turn out to be the ace in the pack.
Richie Blake
Richie Blake.
对他老爸来说
Richard to his father...
- 就象Dick对于别人一样 - 派牌
- Dick to anyone else. - Hit me.
好多年了 都是他老爸给钱他赌
His dad has been funding his son's gambling for years.
现在他也受够了
He's finally had enough.
上星期他告诉我
He confided in me last week...
再帮他一次他就不帮了
the next time he helps his wastrel of a son will be the last.
他每次吹牛 他都有个小动作
Now,when Richie's bluffing,he's got a tell that no one else seems to have spotted.
他都会稍微动一下
He does a little variation each time.
人家都以为是因为他喝醉了
People think it's because he's drunk.
我告诉你这些 你觉得奇怪吧?
Are you wondering why I'm telling you all this?
我是这么想的
The thought had crossed my mind,yeah.
我明天会搞个赌局 赢家拿钱
Well,I'm getting up a little competition tomorrow evening,winner take all.
要25000美金才可以参加 我做庄
25,000 sit-down money.I'll be the dealer.
Chip Lacey跟我说起过
Chip Lacey mentioned something about it.
对的 他也参加 还有Snake Eyes
Yeah,he's in,and Snake Eyes,too.
我不得不找他们 因为这样Richie才会感兴趣
But,you see,I had to get them in,otherwise Richie wouldn't be interested.
我本再多搞几次
I could have done with more time...
但他老爸说了 这是最后一次资助他赌牌
but his father told me it'll be the last drop he gives to Richie.
所以我得快点找到些好牌手
So I had to find a good player,and fast.
你们赌场去死吧
Stick your casino up your ass.
那 你想怎么样?
So,what are you saying?
我想请你也参加
I want to get you in the game.
我出一半的赌金
I'll put in half of the 25,000 sit-down money.
你出另外一半 你赢了钱分给我10%
You put in the other half,then give me 10% of your winnings...
其他就是你的了
and you get to keep everything else.
- 我输了呢? - 你不会的
- What if I lose? - Well,you won't.
第一因为你是很厉害的牌手
A:because you're an exceptional player...
第二因为你会有我
and B:because you've got a sure-fire tell...
来帮你
courtesy of me.
那怎么不找Snake Eyes跟Lacey?
Why not bring Snake Eyes or Lacey in on this with you?
他们是不错
They're good...
但从今晚看来 你更厉害
but from what I saw this evening,you're even better.
计划的不错 但是 我不想去
Nice plan,but no,thanks.
改变了主意就给我电话
In case you change your mind.
好吧?
Right?
应该不会了 我明天飞回荷兰了 谢谢你 Ben
I doubt it.I'm flying home to Holland tomorrow.Thank you anyway,Ben.
没关系
Pleasure.
Stacie
Stacie.
Jake
Jake.
你在这干吗?
What are you doing here?
该我问你吧?
Shouldn't I be asking you that?
- 你还单身 还是...? - 她不是单身
- Are you alone,or are you with... - No.
她跟我一起了
She's with me.
Mickey Stone
Well,well.Mickey Stone.
我听说你死了
I heard you were dead.
想的美
Wishful thinking.
怎么了 Mickey仔 你开始开赌场了?
So what's the story,Mickey-boy?You pulling casinos now?
不是 我过来玩牌
No,I was here to play poker.
- 希望你牌艺好了些 - 是好了些
- I hope your game's improved. - It has.
那你小赌小骗的生意怎么样Jake?
So how are things in the small- con world,Jake?
还在骗些小钱吧?
Still taking ?0 scores?
我不知道喔 我早不玩那些了
I wouldn't know.Some of us managed to get out a long time ago.
但你还占着些不属于你的东西吧
And some of us got out with something that didn't belong to them.
算了Mickey 不要跟这些人再说了
Leave it,Mickey.He's really not worth it.
真的算了?他这么对你
Are you serious,after what he did to you?
我们不是活的蛮好的吗?
I think I came out of it pretty well,considering.
Albert 他上钓了
Albert,he's on the hook.
好的
Good.
- 他会来的 - 好
- He's gone for it. - Nice one.
快点快点
Come on,come on.
我对这一窍不通
That is all double Dutch to me.
好了 开始
Come on,come....We're in.
- 忘带钥匙了? - Stacie
- Forgotten your key? - Hello,Stacie.
再见Jake
Goodbye,Jake.
我来道歉的
I've come to apologize.
- 这道歉晚了5年 - 求你了
- You're five years too late. - Please.
我想该陪你一下
I thought I'd keep you company...
我见到你跟Micky吵架
seeing as though it looks like Mickey's neglecting you.
- 他很快会回来的 - 我不会谈很久的
- He'll be back soon. - It won't take long.
这里风景很好啊
Lovely view.
日子过的挺好吧
You've done well for yourself.
搬来这多久了?
How long you had this place?
我们要去展示单位
The show apartment,please.
好几年了
Couple of years.
看你这身行头 看来我的钱在你 手上也真是用得其所
Nice to see at least my money went on a decent suit.
我还以为婚礼宣誓上你说的是
Although I don't recall the marriage vows saying:
"爱与忠诚
"Love,honor...
"并带走你老婆的所有积蓄"
"and do a runner with your wife's savings."
我做错了 我该罚
Okay.I deserved that.
当然
And that.
他一直在Amsterdam干吗?
So what's he been up to in Amsterdam all this time?
这样说吧 他在那也不是一帆风顺的
Well,put it this way,he hasn't exactly been tiptoeing through the tulips.
他在那开始了赌牌
He made a mint on the poker circuit out there...
好像也没再行骗
and it looks like he's given up grifting.
搞不清有没有
Couldn't take the pace.
这就是我为什么离开
This is why I had to leave.
我赌钱输了 欠Davey Canning很多钱
I owed Davey Canning a lot of money in a poker game.
很多
A lot of money.
我不还他钱 他就给我这
This was a little taste of what was to come if I didn't get him his money.
- 硫酸? - 算好了
- Acid? - I was lucky.
本来要倒到我脸上的
It was meant for my face.
我筹不起钱
I couldn't get all the cash together...
卖了你的房子也不够
not even after selling the house.
我当时好绝望
I was desperate.
打个电话也好啊
A phone call would have been nice.
- 就算是张明信片也好啊 - 我不能啊
- A postcard,even. - I couldn't call you.
怎么能把你扯进来呢?
I couldn't get you involved in the mess.Would have been dangerous for you.
那晚真不敢相信能在赌场见到你
I couldn't believe it,seeing you in the casino tonight.
那是上天注定的?
Must be fate,eh?
是我霉气
Or seriously bad karma.
你想Stacie会不会又回到他身边?
You don't think Stacie would fall for him again?
他曾经爱过她
He once had quite a hold on her.
我打过给她 没接
Once bitten....
我没给你打电话
Just because I couldn't call you...
不是说我就不想你了
didn't mean that I stopped thinking about you.
你的(戒指)在那?
Where's yours?
泰晤士河下面
Bottom of the Thames.
好的
Nice.
那你希望我现在在哪?
That where you wish I was right now?
我不知道你会看穿我
I didn't know you could mind-read.
你恨我 我不怪你
I don't blame you for hating me.
你不接吗?
Aren't you going to get that?
让他等等
It can wait.
- 又没接? - 不是
- Twice bitten? - No.
不是打给Stacie 她应该没什么问题的
Not Stacie.I'm sure she's playing it fine.
我想再跟你一起
I'm asking for a second chance.
你还是那么爱开玩笑啊
Good to see your jokes are as warped as ever.
我还爱你
I still love you,Stace.
真好笑
Really warped.
我不是开玩笑
I'm not joking.
我们一起很好的啊 你也知道的了
We're good together,you know we are.
那是好久前的了
That was a long time ago.
我不逼你
Doesn't have to be.
我知道Mickey不适合你
I know Mickey's not right for you.
怎么说?
How?
因为
Because....
你吻我的时候就跟吻他不一样
You wouldn't have kissed me like that if he was.
你是时候走了Jake
I think it was time you were going,Jake.
我想代表我的客户和你碰个面
碰个面
我有个财产要买.买...
对不起,是卖
知道Stacie对Jake值多少钱吗?
Any idea how much Jake took Stacie for,Mick?
25,000
25,000.
- 那 我们骗他上钩了吗? - 好像是
- So,do we have him? - Looks like it.
你还好吧?
You okay?
还是你见到Jake之后 就一直心不在焉?
Or are you sick of being asked that since Jake showed his face?
第一个问题 好 第二个问题 不是
"Yes" to both those questions.
我不知道该不该让你做
I'm not sure if I'd have the bottle to do what you're doing.
- 什么意思? - 我们找条鱼儿
- How do you mean? - Well,trying to take out a mark...
却非要找上你前夫
when the mark just happens to be your ex.
事情发展得 可能会一团糟
Things can get,you know,a bit messy.
感情会胜过理智
Old feelings come to the surface,all that,you know.
我对他没感情了
Except I don't have any feelings for Jake.
你这么忙也肯见我
Good of you to fit me into your busy schedule.
- 5分钟 - 好的
- Five minutes. - Certainly,sir.
不会太久的 你想怎样?
I haven't got long,Jake.What do you want?
过的蛮不错吧
Done well for yourself,Mick.
还算可以
Can't take all the credit.
没Stacie我也没有今天
Wouldn't have got where I am today without Stacie.
你跟Stace还没到那份上 是吧?
Mind you,you haven't quite got all the trappings,have you?
她现在还没跟你结婚吧
You and Stace still not hitched yet.
那是为什么呢 她不想跟你?
What's the story with that?You got cold feet?
我们一直没找着你去签离婚协议
You haven't exactly made it easy for us to find you,to get the divorce papers.
可能Stacie不想离婚
Perhaps Stacie doesn't want a divorce.
我得说 她还不是很想嫁你
I must admit,she didn't sound so keen on the idea of marrying you.
你又怎么知道?
And how the hell would you know?
她还没告诉你 我昨晚去她屋了吧?
She didn't tell you I was in your apartment last night?
你该走了吧
I think you've outstayed your welcome.
我还没说我想干嘛呢...
You haven't heard my proposition yet.
我不关心
Not sure I'm interested.
我想你会关心的
I think you might be.
- 我再给你一次机会 - 什么机会?
- I'm gonna give you a second chance. - Second chance at what?
今晚有场赌局 赢家拿钱
There's a big poker game tonight.Winner takes all.
就几个人参加
A few other players involved.
我想再给你一次机会 看你能不能打败我
I thought you might like another chance at trying to beat me after all these years.
为什么你觉得我会有兴趣?
What makes you think I care?
有个叫Ben Morgan的搞的赌局 他会做庄
Guy called Ben Morgan set it up.He's gonna be the dealer.
25000的赌金
25,000 gets you a place at the table.
我干吗要跟一个你介绍的庄家赌?
Why would I play in a game with a dealer of your choice?
你以为我会骗你啊?
You think I'm gonna try and cheat you?
- 一次不忠 百次不用 - Mickey 我不需要骗你
- Once a grifter,always a grifter. - No,Mickey.I don't need to cheat you.
我用这
I use this.
你以为你能把人骗倒
You think you're smarter than the next man...
因为你比他聪明 比他厉害
that you can outplay him,that you can outwit him...
但事实上是
but the truth of the matter is...
你还是要输给我
you're still a two-bit loser...
骗一两个笨人去得到你想要的
pulling cons on stupid marks to get what you want.
- 我就不会这样做 - 我倒没有骗Stacie
- I'm out of that game. - I didn't have to con Stacie.
是的
True.
只是当初我没在的 所以根本没人跟你比
Then again,I wasn't around,so there wasn't any competition.
你现在就想来抢了?想的美吧
And the competition's back now?You flatter yourself,Jake.
在Stacie这事上你赢不了我
You just can't handle me being around Stacie.
没关系 你回心转意的时候 给我打个电话
No problem.You give me a call when you get your bottle back.
如果要这样才能让你死心 那好 算我一份
If that's what it takes to get rid of you,then yes,you count me in.
我是Ben Morgan
Ben Morgan.
Jake!
不 不 还不算太迟
No,no!It's not too late,no.
好的 到时见
Okay.Let's meet.
鱼儿上钩了
We're on.
好了 就赌德州扑克 我们都会玩吧?
Okay,holdem it is.Are we all clear on the rules?
不会的可要注意了
I hope you're paying attention.
谢谢
Thank you.
游戏开始 每个玩家有两张牌 面朝下
At the start of the game,every player gets two cards,face down.
之后是跳牌
Then comes the flop.
再开三张
Burn one,place three up.
现在你要下注
At each stage,you place a bet to stay in the game.
之后 要么开牌 要么再跳一张
Next,the turn card,or fourth street.
开最后一张
Then the river.
游戏玩法是
Now,the idea is:
在你手上的牌跟台面上的牌里
between the cards you've got in your hand and the cards on the table...
选最好的5张做一手
you make the best five-card poker hand.
好玩就在于
Tricky thing is:
你不知道其他人的两张牌是什么
you've no idea of knowing what two cards every other player has.
你会说你手上的是最好的牌
So you bet that you've got the best hand...
你下注之后 别的玩家会跟
and once you bet,the other player has to put in the same amount...
大你 或者不跟
raise,or fold.
当然 如果你觉得你手上的是最好的牌
Of course,if you think you've got the best hand....
那全下好了
All in.
别急嘛 这么猛
Easy,tiger.
我全下了因为我觉得他在吹牛
I've gone all in because I believe he's bluffing.
他没好牌的 我倒是有一对Q
He's got a nothing hand,whereas I have pocket queens...
再加上台面上的Q 我就有三张Q
and with the queen in the flop,that makes three of a kind.
他以为我吹牛皮
He thinks I'm bluffing...
但是 我早就把他看穿了
but listen,I can read this kid like a book.
幸亏的是 我还有一对10 不太坏
Good thing is,I got pocket 10s.Which is not bad at all.
我肯定能赢的
I'm sure I've got him beat.
如果 他输了
Now,if he loses....
他输了 他就出局了 因为他手上没钱了
Now,if he loses this,he's out,'cause he's put all his chips in.
他不只输了这一手 他没得玩了
He ain't just lost the hand,he's lost the whole goddamn game.
所以我就赢了
So I win.
你要跟还是不跟啊?
You going to play the hand or not?
好吊啊 不是吗?好我跟
Touchy sod,isn't he?Right,I'll call.
- 他在吹牛皮 - 他在吹牛皮
- He's bluffing. - He's bluffing.
3个Q
Three queens...
赢了一对10
beats a pair of 10s.
就是这样 我会配合你骗倒他的
Here's the deal.I'm gonna come in on this con with you.
骗他?这样说太不客气了吧?
Con?But isn't that rather ungentlemanly?
不如说是一次机会
I'd like to think of it as an opportunity.
我会抓紧这次机会
I've decided to use this "opportunity"...
我会带个人上来
to bring someone else into the competition tonight.
Mickey Stone
Mickey Stone.
谁是Mickey Stone?
And who is Mickey Stone?
这人有我想要的东西
Someone who's got something that I want.
越多人就赢越多罗
The more players in the game,the more money in the pot.
- 对我跟你来说还不是更好 - 对啊
- All the better for you and me. - Exactly.
我就关心这 钱越多就越好
Which is why I'm only interested if we make the pot bigger.
- 多少? - 50000
- How much? - 50,000 sit-down.
50000?
50,000?
我倒想看看其他人能凑够这钱吗
I'll have to see if the other players can come up with that in time.
怎样?
Well?
- 你跟我的一起 100000 - 加上Ben Morgan一份 25000
- Yours and my stake,that's 100,000. - Plus Ben Morgan's stake,25,000.
我们全副身家放进去了
We've already put all our reserve capital into this.
- 没有啊 还有我的养老金呢 - 不是把Albie 开玩笑吧
- Not quite.There's my pension fund. - No,Albie,don't even think about it.
这次是为了你 记住了吗?你最好放醒目点
This one was for you,remember?I mean,you're worth every penny,my dear.
这是我准备六月的医保的钱
And there's the money I set aside for June's hospital bills.
你不能这样做
You can't do that,Ash.
我想我们会赢回来的
I can if I think I'll get it back,which I know we will.
就靠你了Stace
Think of the returns,Stace.
但是我们输的话 我们就全都没了
Yeah,but if we lose,we lose everything we've got.
我们不会输的
We won't lose.
如果Albert能说服
So,if Albert can convince Snake Eyes and Chip Lacey...
每人带上35000来赌局
to come up with an extra 35,000 each for a place at the table....
- 那没问题了 - 我们还差
- Already done. - Then we need to find....
算上我们手头上的 我们还差20000
With what we've got so far,we're still short by 20,000.
只有3个小时了
Three hours to find it.
我要来领我老板的狗的 他老婆今早带过来的
I'm coming in to collect my boss' dog.His wife brought her in this morning.
对了 就是他
Yeah,that's her.
Mitzi
Mitzi.
我待会过来拿
I'll be around to collect her shortly.
好的 待会见 谢谢 再见
Okay,yeah.I'll see you soon.Thank you ever so much.Bye.
- 时间好紧喔 - 你不是喜欢挑战吗
- This is going to be tight. - I thought you liked a challenge.
对啊 我还喜欢Cameron Diaz呢
Yeah,I do.I like Cameron Diaz as well.
但是我没机会啊 知道吗?
Don't mean I stand a chance of copping off with her,does it?
- 告诉你 我不知道 - 来啊 美女
- Mind you,I don't know. - Come on,beautiful.
来了
Here you go.
好的 谢谢罗
All right,thanks a lot.
真是巧夺天工啊
They're all divine.
慢慢挑选
Please take as long as you need to decide.
要先看一下这吗
Perhaps you'd like to have a look at these.
很不巧 我们没时间了
Unfortunately,time is of the essence.We do have a plane to catch.
我只是决定不了
I just can't make up my mind,darling.
快拉 就给你30秒
Pumpkin,you have 30 seconds.
我们要到Harrods去买婴儿床跟婴儿椅
We have to go to Harrods and get the playpen and the crib.
我要这
I'll have this one.
还是这呢?
Or this one?
好的 就那样拉 走了 我们得走了
Okay,that's it.Come on.We have to go.
- 来了 对不起 - 亲爱的
- Come on,I'm sorry. - Sweetie?
你服务很周到 谢谢
You've been most helpful,thank you very much.
- 好拉 我两分钟就好了 - 我说过30秒
- Look,I'll be two minutes. - No,I said 30 seconds.
- 不要急着买啊 - 好了 我们可以再回来的
- You can't hurry a decision like that. - Yeah,well,maybe we'll come back.
我保证
I promise,darling.
- 我这次会定下来的 - 好的
- I'll decide this time. - Okay.
不是吧 你说你已经定下了
Come on,you said you'd made up your mind.
要不要也试试这?
Perhaps madam would like to try one on?
我就知道你不该那么紧张的
I knew you should have been taking it easy.
好了 我没事
No.I'm fine.
- Mitzi 照看好他喔 - 好了Mitzi好了 没事
- Mitzi.Be careful with her. - All right,Mitzi,all right,baby.
- 对不起 - 不要动
- Sorry. - Stay.
- 怎么样? - 没事 我出去呼吸一点新鲜空气
- How you feeling? - I'm fine,I just need some air.
好的 你就在车上等吧
Okay,then you can wait in the car.
- 好了 我们走吧 - 但我的
- Here we go.Come on. - But my....
这天够忙的
It's been a heavy day.
- Mitzi! - 我来照看它
- Mitzi! - I'll take care of the dog.
你能陪她上车吗?谢谢
Would you mind just escorting her to the car?Thank you.
对不起 浪费了你的时间
I am so sorry to have wasted your time.
可能我们下次来伦敦时候会再过来的
Maybe we'll try to come back when we're next in London.
我能给点意见吗
If it helps...
我觉得你夫人会比较喜欢这个
I believe your wife was about to opt for this one.
你觉得吧?
You think?
要是你错了的话我可花费不起喔
Could be a very expensive mistake if you're wrong.
这样吧 何不让我去问一下她?
Tell you what,why don't I go and ask her?
很快的 好吗?
Shouldn't take a second.Yeah?
当然没问题
Of course,sir.
很快回来
I'll be a second.
- 就说我们能凑到 - 好了 游戏开始了
- Told you we'd do it. - Okay,game on.
第一步
Stage one:
我们要让其他两个参加的人先退出
we need to take the other two players out of the competition first.
他们可是不情愿离开的
They won't want to leave the table.
这么轻易就走的话 他们的钱就化汤了
If they leave before the game is over,they forfeit their chips...
所以动动手脚
so they'll need a push.
Danny 你搞定Snake Eyes?
Danny,you're taking care of Snake Eyes?
好的 我跟Eddie 会搞定的
Yeah,me and Eddie got a little something sorted.
我们会让他分身不下的
Let's just say his mind will be on more pressing matters.
好的 Ash 你搞定Chip Lacey?
Okay.Ash,Chip Lacey?
好的 都准备好了 他就等着来点惊喜吧
Yeah,everything's in place.He's in for a small surprise.
之后我们就进行第二步计划 假的小动作
Good.Then we move on to stage two:the false tell.
那会是什么?
What is the tell?
- 天啊 - 告诉我他不是说真的
- Oh,God! - Please tell me he's not serious.
不关我事
Nothing to do with me.
我是大智若愚吧
I thought it was bordering on genius,myself.
大智若愚 那动动脑子
Well,think of something else,genius.
那应该是 不知道呢 眼尾跳一下吧
All right,it'll be something,I don't know,a little bit,you know,twitchy.
好了 那还差不多
Okay,I suppose that's a bit more like it.
我们让Jake先按着Danny的猫腻 赢一点钱,那他才会信我的
We let Jake win on a few of Danny's tells,so he'll know he can trust me.
好啊
Good.
Danny让他上钩后 就离开赌局
Once Danny's let Jake beat him,he'll be out of the game...
就剩下Jake跟我了
and it'll just be Jake and me.
这时就是我们的天下了 对吧 Stacie?
At which point,we'll play our joker.Stacie?
我想赌局前再过去看他一次
I think that I should pay Jake one more visit before the game.
有必要吗?
Is that really necessary?
我觉得有
I think so.
好了 你现在引他上钩了
Well,you've already reeled him in.
我们可是全副身家放进去了的 我得确认一下
We're gambling everything we've got on this.I need to be sure.
对不起
Excuse me.
对 你好
Ja.Hello.
我很荣幸...
此善举是我所能接受的
你的工作实在太重要了
对
Yes!
我真不相信我为了3镑做这事
I can't believe I'm doing this for 3 an hour.
你得记得 你以前从未见过我们
All you got to remember,yeah,is you ain't seen me or any of us before.
- 听到了吧? - 听到了
- Got it? - Got it.
今晚这就只是一家普通的酒吧
So tonight this is just a regular bar.
- 知道了? - 知道了
- Yeah? - Yeah.
你没见过我 知道吗?
You ain't seen me,right?
- 知道了 - 好的
- Right. - Good lad.
Ed 我之前有把我的笔留在这吗?
Ed,did I leave my pen here the other night?
是支金笔 很贵重的
It's a gold one.Very expensive.
我想没有 我之前都没见过你
I shouldn't think so.I've never seen you in here before.
- 不 我想我真把它落这里了 - 不 从来没见过你
- No,really,I think I left it. - Nope.Never seen you.
不 Ed 别玩了 好吧?
No,Ed,stop pissing about now,yeah?
对不起 伙计
Sorry,lad.
Mickey 知道你在这吗?
Does Mickey know you're here?
不
No.
他跟你谈过那赌局吗?
Has he told you about the poker game?
对
Yeah.
我会赢他的
I'm gonna beat him,you know.
- 凭什么这么肯定? - 我惹烦他了
- Why so sure? - I bother him.
你想他干吗要来赌?
Why do you think he's taking the game on?
是我逼他的
I get to him,always have done.
他就总是二流货色
Mickey's always gonna be second best...
特别是在你面前
especially where you're concerned.
你干吗这样干?
Why are you doing this,Jake?
我要你回我身边
I want you back.
不可能
That's not gonna happen.
你每一寸肌肤我都亲过
I know every inch of you,Stace.
你的气味 你的想法 我都熟悉
I know the way you smell.I know the way you think.
我还知道你说谎的时候就喜欢 用手梳头发
And I know the way you put your hands through your hair when you're lying.
Micky是没办法赢我的
There's no way Mickey's gonna beat me.
对赌我很熟悉 没一步都很熟悉
I know every con,every move.
不论他怎么做 我都会赢的 你是知道的
Whatever he comes up with,I'm gonna beat him,and you know that.
不是吗?
Don't you?
好了 那取消好了
Well,then call it off.
为什么?
Why?
因为我不想他受伤
Because I don't want him hurt.
太迟了
Too late.
不要 Jake 我说真的
Please,Jake.I mean it.
- 取消吧 - 你是因为这才来这的 对吧?
- Call it off. - That's why you've come here,isn't it?
来就你的爱人
To save lover-boy.
- 你走了之后 他过来了 - 我打赌他也不相信这
- He was there for me when you left. - I bet he couldn't believe his luck.
你说 你说 你还爱我
What you said,when you said you still love me.
- 是真的吗? - 对
- Did you mean it? - Yeah.
用我生命来担保
On my life.
- 那有什么不同吗? - 没
- Does that make a difference? - No.
一个机会也不给?
Not even a maybe?
一个机会也不给
Not even a maybe.
- 这是我的25000 - 我的25000
- Here's my 25,000. - 25,000 from me.
- 你想参一手吧? - 来了
- Do you wanna buy in,lads? - Game on.
好了
There you go.
- 差点来不了 - 怎么样?
- Nearly had to stand down. - How come?
我还来赌牌 我老婆快疯了
My wife's going crazy,me coming out playing cards...
还有两个礼拜就预产期了
two weeks before the baby's due.
我每天24小时随时候命
I'm on call,24/7.
这是Mickey
That's Mickey.
放松 Ben 你太做作了
Relax,Ben,you make it obvious.
对不起
I'm sorry.
- 晚上好各位 要点什么吗? - 我要一杯果汁
- Evening,sir.What can I get you? - Just an orange juice for me,please,and...
Stace我给你点了杯Kir Royale 知道你以前很爱喝的
I've ordered you a Kir Royale,Stace,just for old times' sake.
Ben 这是Mickey Stone 跟可爱的Stacie
Ben,this is Mickey Stone and the lovely Stacie.
- Stacie - Stacie以前跟我在一起很久了
- Stacie. - Stacie and I go back a long way.
- 真的? - 对 不过那是很久前的事了
- Really? - Yeah.Still,that was a long time ago.
之后很多事都变了 Stacie也是
A lot's changed since then,including Stacie.
我以前也很喜欢你穿这样的颜色的
I used to love you in that color.
你没事吧?
You stacked?
这是Chip Lacey
This is Chip Lacey.
你好Chip
Hi,Chip.
穿西装的那人是
And the guy in the specs there:Snake Eyes.
Snake Eyes.
- 你东西都装好了? - 当然
- Did you pack your bags yourself,sir? - Absolutely.
看来你朋友不大想来了吧
It doesn't look like your friend is going to turn up.
我们何不开始算了?没他一样
Why don't we just start without him?
别担心 他会来的 只是他就是那么拖拉的
Don't worry,he'll be here.He's just a little tardy.
我干吗还要给小费?
Why don't I keep the change?
我走都比你开得快
I could have swum here bloody quicker than that!
不好意思迟了点
Bit late.Sorry,lads.
你请个酒鬼来?
Interesting euphemism for "drunk."
- 你终于来了 - 对啊 终于来了
- Decent of you to turn up. - Oh,I've managed.
你知道吗?我是不到点不出现的
You know what they say,lads.No show without Punch,is there?
好了 这地方难找死了
Anyway,it took me bleeding ages to find this place.
你好妹妹 我不知道还有个妹妹会在这
Hello,love.I didn't realize there was ladies present.
你好吗 心肝?
You all right,sweetheart?
Cor 是很漂亮喔 对吧?
Cor,that's cute,isn't it?
这是什么鬼地方啊?
So,what kind of a poxy old joint is this,then?
我就是这鬼地方的主人
I'm the owner of this poxy joint.
好了 听着 我要一大杯苏格兰酒 加冰
Right.Listen up,squire,I want a large Scotch,nice and big,bit of ice.
先记帐 然后再给你自己来一杯
Stick it on a tab,get one yourself.
行吗 Jim?
All right,Jim?
叫我Jake
It's Jake.
随便了 想叫什么都可以
Yeah,whatever.Tell you what,lads.
希望你今晚能有好运气 因为我觉得我最近都很好运气
Hope you got your lucky boots on,'cause I'm feeling lucky tonight.
今晚我会好运气吗?当然会
Are you feeling lucky tonight?Yes,I am !
好了 赌局玩德州扑克 赢家拿钱
All right,name of the game is Texas hold 'em.Winner takes all.
输了就把你的钱留下 没得玩了
Leave the table or you lose your stake,you're out of the game.
每有一个人输的话我们就休息一下
Only after each player is out will I call a break.
- 清楚了? - 清楚了
- Clear? - Crystal clear.
准备好了吧 各位?
Ready,gentlemen?
大你
Raise you.
- 不跟 - 好的
- Fold. - All right.
跟
Call.
跟?你想输就让你输
Calling,are we?Start as you mean to go on.
我大1000
I'll raise 1,000.
你听到了
You know what they say.
你就得以牙还牙 对吧 甜心?
You gotta make action to get action.Isn't that right,sweetheart?
不跟
Fold.
好了 Ray Charles退出了
All right,Ray Charles is out.
不跟
Fold.
跟
Call.
一对
A pair.
三张赢
Three of a kind wins the game.
算你运气
Mr.Lucky.
谢谢你过来.很抱歉时间晚了些
我的妻子已经离开很久了 但我带来了所有的...
和公寓相关的文件
一条
Flush.
来点咖啡好吧
Now would be a good time for coffee.
好 那我再来一杯苏格兰酒
Yeah,and I'll have another large Scotch.
来 Benny 给我些好运气
Come on,Benny,deal me something lucky,son.
我想我还会赢的
Think I'll have another one.
谢谢
Thanks,cowboy.
妈的
Shit.
摘下你的眼镜吧 那样你会看得更清楚
Take your glasses off,you might be able to see better.
到Snake Eyes下注
Snake Eyes to bet.
- 跟 - 好的
- Call. - All right.
一对 满好牌的
It's a pair.Wow,good deal.
到你
To my left.
2,000
2,000.
到Mick
To the Mick.
跟
Call.
好 来了
Oh,well,that's something.
大你40000
Raise 40,000.
40,000?那可是一大笔钱 不是吗 Snakey?
40,000?That's a lot of money,ain't it,Snakey?
- 你没事吧?看上去你 - 我没事
- You all right,mate?You look a bit... - I'm fine.
跟
Call.
我也来
Yeah,I'll have a bit of that.
谢谢 不用找了
Thanks,mate,keep the change.
黑桃J
Black jack.
全下
All in.
有人要走了
We have lift-off.
跟
Call.
A
Ace high.
你不是吧
You must be joking.
- 就凭这你全下了? - 一色 赢
- You went all in on that? - Flush takes it.
对不起Snake 你输了
Sorry,Snake,you're out of the game.
我知道
Don't I know it.
看来他很急着要走啊
Well,he seemed in a hurry to leave us.
先休息两分钟再继续
Two-minute break before the next hand.
来 来
Come on,come on.
对了 Ed 是我
Yeah,Ed,it's me.
他们怎么样了?我该打电话了吧?
What are they up to?Is it time?
好的 我会搞定
Okay,I'm on it.
－别接了 －对不起 我得接的
- Leave it alone. - Sorry,I gotta take it.
喂?
Hello?
你是谁?
Who is this?
她快生了 我想你最好快过来
She's not far off now,Mr.Lacey.I think you'd better get over here.
- 她要见你 - 这样 好的
- She's asking for you,yes. - Yeah,all right.
妈的
Shit,shit.
不跟
Fold.
全下了 20000
All in.20,000.
你输了
You're out of the game.
休息一下
Break.
来杯水
Glass of water,please.
你觉得Micky开始起疑心了吗?
Do you think Mickey suspects anything?
- 怀疑什么? - 我们的事啊
- Such as? - Between us.
我们之间没事
There is no "us."
没有吗?
Isn't there?
你知道我想怎样吗?
Do you know what I wish,Jake?
怎样?
What?
我想你最好一直都没出现过
That you'd never shown up at all.
我已经忘了你了 但你一出现
I'd almost managed to forget about you,and yet here you are...
就把我的生活搞得乱七八糟的
messing up my life again.
有多糟呢?
How exactly am I messing it up?
你把我搞糊涂了
Because you've got me so confused.
还有呢?
About what?
Mickey
Mickey.
他们想骗你
They're trying to con you.
就是为这我之前去你酒店找你
That's why I came to your hotel room earlier.
想叫你别来了
To try to get you to stop playing.
除了刚走的两个 他们都是认识的
They all know each other,apart from the two who are already out.
Richie会有些小动作 那是假的 这样才能骗你
Richie's gonna give you a false tell,then they'll wait till you've gone all in.
Richie会拿一副好牌
Richie will have a better hand than you...
然后就做些小动作 让你觉得是副烂牌
but you're supposed to think it's a poor hand.
这样就能骗到你了
The "sure-fire tell" isn't so sure-fire after all.
如果Richie输了 我就坐在Mickey后面
So,once Richie's out,I'll stand behind Mickey...
告诉你他有什么牌
and indicate to you what cards he's got in his hand.
你干吗告诉我这些?
Why exactly are you telling me this?
因为我相信你爱我
Because I believed you when you said you loved me.
我是爱你
I do.
不是吧 在重拾旧欢啊?
Don't tell me.You're catching up on old times?
差不多
Something like that.
Jake 算了吧
Jake,give it up.
什么?
Sorry?
想去拿不属于你的东西 那是浪费时间
Trying to take what doesn't belong to you.You're wasting your time.
30,000.
- 我想你在吹牛 - 那跟啊
- I think you're bluffing. - Call me,then.
我会的
I'll call you.
那你就给我钱了
Give it to me,boy.Oh,yeah.
我会跟
I'll go all in.
跟
Call.
- 输了吧? - 3个6
- Suck on them. - Three sixes.
同花顺
Straight flush.
骗人吧
It's a fix.
你输了
You're out,Richie.
我从未见过有人有同花顺
I've never seen anybody get a straight flush.
跟他杯香槟 我请
Get him a champagne,please.On me.
Benny 你是个老千
Benny,you're a bottom-card dealer and a bum.
我不跟你们这些业余玩了
I'm not playing any of you amateurs.
剩下你跟我了Mickey 你觉得你走运了吧?
Just you and me,Mickey.You feeling lucky?
Jake 我不信命运
Jake,I don't rely on luck.
休息两分钟 各位
Two-minute break,gentlemen.
好了 各位
Time,gentlemen.
依老规矩
Just like old times.
现在你没这么自信了吧Jake?
You're really feeling that confident,Jake?
我对手比我强的时候我才会不自信的
Only when I'm playing someone who thinks he's better than me.
我想你会输喔
I think you're the one who's about to go down.
我真喜欢这
I'm really gonna enjoy this.
你知道吗?我也是喔
Well,you know what?So am I.
Stace 关于我们谈起的那事
Stace,that thing we talked about.
算了 我不要人帮
Forget it.I don't need any help.
我要堂堂正正赢他
I feel like playing this thing for real.
什么?
What?
坐到吧台那边吧
Go and take a seat at the end of the bar.
去
Go on.
有什么不对劲 都可以提出取消赌局喔
If there's any suggestion of impropriety,I'll call the game off.
不 继续吧
No,you will not.
发牌
Deal the cards.
来 发牌
Come on,deal!
10,000
10,000.
跟
Call.
15,000
15,000.
跟
Call.
40,000
40,000.
跟
Call.
红桃Q
Red lady.
逼得自己没退路了吧?
Painted yourself in a bit of a corner there,haven't you,Mickey?
你以为啊?
You think so?
我是这样认为的
I know so.
告诉你
I'll tell you what.
你何不全下 我跟进?
Why don't you go all in and I'll call?
好 全下
Yeah,all in.
跟
Call.
顺
Straight.
9 10 J Q
Nine,ten,jack,queen...
K
king.
是顺
It's a straight.
10 J Q
A ten,a jack,a queen...
K
a king...
还有A
and an ace.
真不够运气啊Mickey
Bad luck,Mickey.
Ben?
- 谢谢你 - 没关系
- Thank you,Ben. - Anytime.
Michael 你来荷兰的话 记得找我
Michael,if you're ever in Holland,do call me.
我教你怎么玩
I'll teach you how to play properly.
你跟我走吧?
You coming?
Stacie?
怎么回事?
What's going on?
我觉得这是最好的了
I just think that this is for the best.
你要谅解我
Please try to understand.
这是我第二次机会了
It's my second chance.
我不知道怎么说 我还爱他
I don't know what to say.I still love him.
算了吧 Mickey...
And let's face it,Mickey...
你从来没想过要我 对吧?
you never really wanted me,did you?
但Jake想过
And Jake does.
这不是很好吗?我意思是 应该就要这样
This is a wind-up,right?I mean,it has to be.
- 我们走吧 - Stacie?
- Let's go. - Stacie?
对不起 Danny,Albie
I'm sorry,Danny,Albie.
我保证我会拿回你们的钱的
I will make sure you get your money back,I swear.
Eddie 把外套递给我 好吗?
Eddie,can I have my coat,please?
真不敢相信
I can't believe it.
就这样?Stacie走了 还有那钱啊?
Is that it?Stacie's gone,and so is the money?
Mickey 这不是真的
Mickey,this can't be happening.
去Heathrow 开快点
Heathrow,mate,as quick as you can.
我不要收拾一下吗?
Shouldn't we pick up some of my stuff first?
这样Mickey就能跟上来了吧?
And let Mickey catch up to us?
糟了 Jake!
No,Jake!
我发誓我也不知道 我不知道他们会这样做
I swear I didn't know.I didn't know they were going to do that.
调头
Change of plan.
我想这是属于我的
I think that belongs to me.
想的美啊 Mickey
Nice try,Mickey.
Mickey...
给他吧
give it to him.
真不敢相信你会这样做
I can't believe you're doing this.
Stacie 无论他跟你说什么 别相信啊
Stacie,whatever he's promised you,don't fall for it.
Stacie 我问你 我求你了
Stacie,I'm asking you,I am begging you...
别这样做
please do not do this.
我们没你了怎么办?
What the hell are we going to do without you?
对不起
I'm sorry.
我又赢你了吧?
Not the only thing I won off you again,is it?
你赢我了?
You "won" me?
好像我是个奖品似的
Makes it sound like I'm a prize in some raffle.
对 可是你是最好的啊
Yeah,but you'd be the first prize.
- 谢谢 - 只是开个玩笑 没关系吧?
- Thanks. - It's a joke.Does it matter?
最重要的是我们又一起了
The main thing is that we're back together again.
有关系
It matters to me.
你是这样看我的啊 Jake?
Is that how you see me,Jake?
就像个奖杯 好让你能在人家面前炫耀啊?
As a trophy you can show off to your friends when it suits you?
不是,Stace
Come on,Stace.
你一直都是那么想的 对吧?
That's what this has all been about,hasn't it?
- 什么? - 你就知道钱 就知道赢
- What? - Money,winning...
把我从Mickey手上抢过来
getting one over on Mickey.
你们两一样差劲
You're both as bad as each other.
你根本不想要我的 对不?
It wasn't about wanting me back at all,was it?
我当然想
Of course it was.
我是说 想要我
I mean,really wanting me.
是真的
Of course it was.
那证明吧
Prove it.
- 怎样证明? - 我对你那么重要
- How? - lf I mean so much to you...
那把钱扔了
get rid of the money.
来 如果你爱我 把钱扔了
Go on.If you love me,throw it out into the river.
什么?
What?
我想你不会的
I didn't think you would.
好的
All right.
满意了吧?
Satisfied?
我还以为
There was a moment there...
还以为你对我是真心的
when I thought that you were genuine.
如果你是真的
And if you had been...
谁会知道我们之间会发生什么啊?
who knows what might have happened between us?
我真够笨的
I was stupid enough to think that you'd changed...
你从来就没变过
but you will never,ever change.
那些全是假钞 对不对?
That was the case full of fake money,wasn't it?
再见 Jake
Goodbye,Jake.
- 至少让我补偿一下你 - 我一点都不想要钱
- At least let me give you what I owe you. - I don't give a damn about the money.
我从来就没想过要
I never did.
走吧
Just get out.
我的外套 Eddie
My coat,please,Eddie.
Danny 她干吗拿了一叠假钱?
Danny,does her taking one of these mean anything to you?
等一下
Hang on a second.
我知道她在干吗了
I know what she's doing.
糟了 Jake!
No,Jake!
我发誓我不知道 我不知道他们会这样做
I swear I didn't know.I didn't know they were going to do that.
调头
Change of plan.
你回来了 真好
Good to have you back,my dear.
你就是能突发奇想
You always could think on your feet,Stace.
Stacie就知道她要干什么的
Stacie knew what she was doing.
- 我从未怀疑过她 - 很高兴听到这
- I never doubted her. - Glad to hear it.
我们该等等Danny吗?
Shouldn't we wait for the kid?
最好等一下 不然他会生气的
Yeah,better had.He'll only sulk.
要等一下 他去拿钱了
Yeah,he might be a little while.He's gone fishing.
- 正上来 - 好了
- On his way up. - Here we go.
那么 你到底干了什么?
So,what exactly have you been up to?
我只是以牙还牙吧了
Let's just say I've been dotting the "I's" and crossing the "T's," that's all.
Ash?
我知道你也不想
I understand if you don't want to do this...
但只有你跟他最熟悉了
but you know him better than anybody else.
继续说
Go on.
Jake给你留下了些什么让你感触的东西?
First,what were these thoughtful touches that Jake left you?
房子卖了之后
Well,after selling the house...
也把我银行帐户也清了
and cleaning out the bank account...
就留给我一盘仙人掌
all he left me was a cactus...
一张Phil Collins的CD...
a Phil Collins CD...
和一份硬芝士
and a moldy piece of cheese.
你都那样放了?
You did all that for me?
对啊 他活该啊 不是吗?
Yeah,well,it's not like he didn't deserve it,is it?
- 给没来的朋友? - 为什么不?
- To absent friends? - Why not?
- 干杯 - 干杯
- Cheers. - Cheers.
很好玩啊?谁把衣服带走了?
Very funny.Who nicked me clothes?
可怜的Danny啊
Poor Danny!
你就这样经过接待处啊?
Did you have to walk past the receptionist like that?
是的 就这样
Yes,I did.
但是我拿到她电话了喔
I did get her phone number,though.
- 厉害 - 大家都做得好
- Well done,all. - Well done,boys.
来
Open it up.
Hello!